export const countriesData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Bridgetown is the capital of this popular country.`,
        hints: ['It is a popular Carribbean country.', 'Popular artist and business-woman Rihanna was born and raised there.'],
        answer: 'Barbados',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which country covers the most time zones?`,
        hints: ['This country is located in Europe', 'They speak French.'],
        answer: 'France',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which country has no rivers?`,
        hints: ['It is located in the Middle East.', 'No second hint available. You may call on a team mate.'],
        answer: 'Saudi Arabia',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which country is smaller than Central Park in New York City? `,
        hints: ['This country is located in Europe.', 'No second hint available. You may call on a team mate.'],
        answer: 'Monaco [The Vatican will not be accepted because it is not considered a country.]',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which country has the most languages in the world? `,
        hints: ['No first hint available but you may call someone to help you. If they dont pick up their phone, you can use the second hint or pass on the question.', 'No second hint available. You may call on a team mate.'],
        answer: 'Papua New Guinea, with over 820.',
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which country produces most of the world's oxygen?`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Russia',
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which country produces the most opium? `,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Afghanistan',
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `This country has a population of 1.43 billion. `,
        hints: ['It is an Asian country.', 'No second hint available. You may call on a team mate.'],
        answer: 'China',
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `This country is the world's largest island nation.`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Indonesia',
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: ` This country invented bread in 8,000 BC.`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Egypt',
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Kenneth Kuanda was the first president of this country. `,
        hints: ['This country is located in Central Africa.', 'No second hint available. You may call on a team mate.'],
        answer: 'Zambia',
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `In which country are Tangier and Casablanca? `,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Morocco',
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which country, bordering Zaire, takes its name from the former name of the Zaire river? `,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Democratic Republic of Congo',
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which country is home to Kilimanjaro, the highest mountain in the continent of Africa?`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Tanzania',
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Angola achieved independence from this European country in 1975? `,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Portugal',
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Nairobi is the capital of which country? `,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Kenya',
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Which African country is bordered by Benin, Ghana, Ivory Coast, Niger, and Mali?`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Burkina Faso',
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `This country has more Portuguese speakers than Portugal.`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Angola',
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `This country is home to Lac Rose, also known as Pink Lakes.`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Senegal',
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Everyone who lives in this European country, even foreigners, can attend college tuition-free.`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Germany',
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `This Southeast Asian country is one of only three in the world, along with Liberia and the United States, that does not use the metric system.`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Myanmar',
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `Kimchi and rice are the two most important foods of this East Asian nation.`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'South Korea',
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        type: 'fill in blank',
        question: `This country is home to Caño Cristales, a river in this South American country that is referred to as the “liquid rainbow” because of its many vivid colors, which are produced from the reproductive process of aquatic plants.`,
        hints: ['', ''],
        answer: 'Columbia',
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        type: 'multiple choice',
        question: `This country’s musical tradition inspired the “birth of blues” in the United States.`,
        options: ['Ghana', 'Mali', 'South Africa', 'Ethiopia'],
        answer: 'Mali',
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        type: 'multiple choice',
        question: `Which historic paradise is the birthplace of “Rai” music’s mix of Arabic scales and synthesized disco effects?`,
        options: ['Somalia', 'Egypt', 'Algeria', 'Ivory Coast'],
        answer: 'Algeria',
    },
    {
        id: 26,
        type: 'multiple choice',
        question: `Which country's music has been heavily influenced by the Rastafarian, Orthodox Christinatiy and Judaism religions?`,
        options: ['Ethiopia', 'Morocco', 'Benin', 'Cameroon'],
        answer: 'Ethiopia',
    },

]

export default countriesData;